I'm Hirotika Nakagawa, and I transferred from Tokyo.
Nice to meet you.
Ha! More Tokyo scum!
Oh, Hirotika.
Kuya?
Kuya, is that you?
It was a fateful reunion.
Rika thinks it looks perfect!
I agree.
Okay, we got it, guys.
Let's start getting ready for the next scene.
Everybody good to go?
I'm all set here.
Jeez, this is heavy.
Okay, lights, camera, action!
You've got some nerve, you know that!
What? Why, how dare you?
How dare I? How dare you?
Awesome, cut!
Now, what's after this scene?
Hey, Yozara?
Huh?
The sun is setting, so we're losing our light.
Anything we shoot now won't match the other footage.
Hmm.
Well, that's that, then.
Hey, guys!
We'll pick it up tomorrow.
Meet in the clubroom after school.
We're running a little behind, so do not be late.
Okay.
I can't hear you!
Okay!
Yeah!
Thank you.
No scenes with Kotaro today either.
Man, I wish I had a little more screen time.
But being a part of the crew is more fun than I thought it'd be,
so I guess it's all right.
Those must be the score rankings from finals.
Senna scored 895 out of 900.
I didn't know someone could even get a score that high.
Yozura got the highest score in our class, too.
What's that about?
Gross.
Hey, you got some kind of problem, pal?
What? I don't think so. No problem here.
Hold on. You're Senna Kashiwazaki's boyfriend, aren't you?
I, huh?
I know it's true.
Curse that tricky Senna.
If a mortal enemy is a thing, she's totally mine.
I'm getting that.
So no offense, but who are you anyway?
Are you serious? You really don't know who I am?
Good grief.
I suppose I should have expected an associate of Senna's
to be as rude as she is.
Wow. Okay. Are you, like, famous or something?
Should be.
My name's Awa Yusef, student council treasurer,
year two, class three, ranked second.
Oh.
Class three, huh?
That's Senna's class.
You're in the student council and ranked second in our whole grade?
That's impressive.
Your condescending attitude is more than a little obnoxious.
I don't need you to remind me I've been Senna Kashiwazaki's runner-up since last year.
I don't know anything about last year, but this year it looks like you're doing really great.
Senna is just tough, that's all.
Shut up.
So what? I want to win by getting better exam scores, if nothing else.
She's the most glamorous, gets the highest grades ever, and is one of the best athletes at school.
Not to mention she's a rich little princess.
I feel like I've heard all this somewhere before.
That's not the worst part.
I know for a fact she's one of those people with so-called real lives.
Now, on top of that, she's got a boyfriend?
No one person is supposed to get that much.
Her existence is a mockery.
It's not fair, Senna's boyfriend. It's not.
Slow down a second.
I am not now, nor have I ever dated Senna.
Oh, please, don't try to lie to me.
You forget. I've seen the two of you together, and there's obviously something going on there.
The other guys in school can barely even talk to her, yet you have no problem chatting her up left and right.
This chick is not what I'd call a listener.
I mean, jeez. I'm fighting like hell to get a higher score than her.
Meanwhile, she goes out and gets herself a super cool boyfriend.
Like I said, it isn't fair!
A moment, please.
You just referred to her boyfriend as cool.
Are you talking about me?
Uh, do you see anyone else standing there?
I mean, it doesn't matter how you look at it. You're super cool.
There's that natural-looking blonde hair you obviously dye regularly.
And you wear your pants rolled up like the hipster you are.
Some might call it fashion.
The point is, you're clearly another one of those special having-life people because you're so damn cool.
Thank you. Nobody's ever talked to me like that before.
Why are you making that stupid face? Come on!
Great, so on top of being cool, you also have a sense of humor.
I can't help but be impressed, but I hate it so much.
Fine, you win. I'm jealous of both of you.
Mr. Perfect and Little Miss Perfect are perfect, perfect, perfect for each other.
Vomit. I'm so out of here.
So that's Aoi Yusa.
Apparently, this place is freaking packed with weirdos.
Yo, what's up?
Hey, why are you the only one here?
Yozora and Rika left to go scout out a new location for filming.
Something about a shot of the sun setting into the sea.
Uh, hey, on the way here, I ran into a girl named Aoi Yusa checking out the finals rankings.
Who is that person?
You mean you don't already know her? She's in your class.
What?
She's kind of short and has this shortish-reddish hair thing going on.
Oh, yeah. Short and shortish-reddish kind of rings a bell.
You should know the people you're in class with, at least.
Well, I memorized all the names of the girls who sit close to me.
Not that it ever paid off any.
What? Did something happen?
I told you.
There are only two types of girls in this world.
Awesome girls, the kind I can be friends with, and all those other bitches.
Besides, why should I be forced to learn a bunch of mongrels' names?
Why? Don't come.
She calls the people in her class mongrels?
Well, evidently this Aoi girl isn't very happy that she's always listed right below you on every single test ranking.
Why would I care about another student's rank?
Did you see the scores? Where are those things even posted?
On the bulletin board in the courtyard.
Oh, guess that makes sense.
You mean you never looked?
I don't have to. I can tell my rank from the paper that has our percentiles and stuff on it.
The only thing that matters to me is that I come in first.
You really are something.
Yeah, thank you.
What kind of studying do you normally do for your classes? Please tell me you have a tutor.
No way. I don't study outside of school and homework.
You're kidding me. You study for tests, though, right?
Not besides that one time we studied together.
But hey, that was a pretty good time, though, wasn't it?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I guess it was.
So what's the deal?
Did something weird happen with that Aoi girl?
Meh. Never mind.
Okay.
It's weird.
She honestly couldn't care less about anything that doesn't affect her directly.
Yet when she does care about something, she gets so into it, she makes it awkward.
When it comes to Yozara, even if she doesn't like it, she gets practically criminal.
The photos might be criminal.
She lives for what makes her happy and does exactly what she wants.
Doesn't help that she's got a crazy amount of talent and a rich enough family to get away with it all, too.
She's a born princess.
Maybe it's only natural for all the girls in the world to hate her.
Now that I think about it, getting to hang out with her probably is some sort of bizarre divine honor.
We found the perfect location, you guys!
But we have to go there right now.
Game over, neat.
Hey!
Why are you still sitting? Let's go!
Yeah, okay.
And... action!
Get ready, Herotica, because I'm coming strong.
Kuya, what is wrong with you?
Cut!
Okay, we're looking pretty good!
Hey, Rika, are you sure this will work out?
Yeah, why would it not?
I don't know, maybe because we're obviously in a park?
There's no need to worry about that.
Rika's going to use CG later to make it appear like the whole scene's at the beach.
It'll be so fun!
Rika needs to go edit this, so she'll see you later!
Okay, bye then.
I wonder if she'll actually be able to make that beach scene thing work.
I mean, she's a scientist, not a CG expert.
Well, if it isn't Kodika!
Oh, hi, President!
Hi! Fancy seeing you here.
Well, we're at school, so...
Right.
Our festival atmosphere is rather pleasant.
Don't you agree?
Yeah, I guess it is.
Now, if I recall correctly, your club is doing a movie, right?
Yes, sir.
I certainly enjoy a good flick.
And believe it or not, your father used to drag me out to the movies all the time.
Ha!
What's funny?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
Tell me about this movie you're making.
What's it like?
Senna didn't say.
Senna hasn't told you what it's about?
Well, I don't have as much time to speak with her as I'd like.
Cool.
I get that.
When you're done, I'd love to watch the movie, if that's okay.
Sorry.
I'd feel a little awkward having someone I know watch it.
By the way, Kodaka?
Yeah?
I'm curious how your relationship with Senna has been coming along.
Huh?
I'm not sure what you mean.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
I'm a jerk.
Of course you're too embarrassed to talk to me about it.
No, I'm not embarrassed, sir.
It's just that...
What do you mean by...
Our relationship?
Ha!
We're just guys.
You don't have to play dumb with me.
I'm not playing.
Um, I don't...
I'm really confused, sir.
It is my understanding that you and Senna are dating.
Not accurate, sir.
What?
I have to go now.
Sorry, urgent.
See you another day.
Sure.
Damn you, Fade!
What's going on?
Why is everyone so weird?
I don't get it.
Hey, guys.
What's up?
Kodaka, come with me real quick.
Why?
What the hell are you doing, fog lights?
We have to do something.
We'll be right back.
Jeez, Senna, what's your deal?
It's hot.
Yeah, so what are we here for?
I think...
Well, it looks like Daddy thought you and I were dating.
Oh, yeah, I heard.
Yesterday he asked me if we were in a relationship and seemed upset when I told him no.
Do you have any idea where he got that from?
Well, uh, let me think.
I'm not sure how to put this.
Will you please stop glaring at me first, though?
I'm not glaring at you.
I'm just suspicious.
Okay, um, remember how we all went to the amusement park?
Yeah, I remember.
And, well, I got those tickets from Daddy, right?
So you said.
See, when he gave them to me, I said...
Thank you!
Kobito's for sure gonna be my little sister now!
What?
I think that gave Daddy the wrong idea about you and me and stuff.
You're not making sense.
Jeez, why do you have to be so stupid?
Think about it.
If we got married...
Then that would mean I, um...
If we were married, Kobito would literally be my sister.
If we're what?
I guess that's true, but I'm still lost.
And at the time, I was just so excited, I didn't really think all that much about it.
Now, in hindsight, I remember he was acting all weird.
Like he'd ask, are there plans to make Kobito your official sister?
And how has your relationship been progressing?
It was weird.
Sounds that way.
How did you answer him?
Oh, I've got this.
Don't you worry.
Crap.
What?
So it seems he didn't realize I was talking about Kobito.
He kind of thought I was talking about you and me.
Are you serious?
If it helps, I feel really bad about it.
Well, you cleared all that up and explained everything to him, didn't you?
Yeah.
That's good.
As long as he knows it was just a big misunderstanding, I'm sure it'll be fine.
I kind of feel bad for him, but at least he knows the truth.
So, uh, here's what I wanted to talk about.
What?
There's more going on than that?
Mm-hmm.
But for the record, this is absolutely in no way my fault.
You got that?
Daddy only just told me about this because of the crap drama that's been going on between
us lately.
Oh, okay.
Well, he told me that, um, you and I are kind of engaged.
Are you all right?
Uh, oh, yeah, uh-huh.
Daddy says, back when we were too young to remember, he and your dad made this promise
to each other.
Basically, we're what you'd call betrothed.
Betrothed?
What are we, like a freaking soap opera?
Might as well be, since they also decided they should write up a marriage pact and put
our thumbprints on it.
Have you seen this pact?
I have!
Our little prints are pretty adorable.
They're so tiny.
What?
Really?
That's weird.
I don't remember that at all.
I didn't remember either, but it's true.
Hold on.
Here, look.
It's us.
Yep.
It looks like we met way before we thought we did.
How crazy.
Crazy.
That's the word for it.
I can't believe this.
Well, regardless, it doesn't matter.
Nope.
I mean, it's not like we're going to get married.
No way.
Not to mention the fact that we shouldn't have to worry about an engagement we didn't make.
That would just be silly, right?
Yes, totally right.
Our dads are beyond random, and that stuff has nothing to do with us.
It's funny.
When it comes to my dad, well, knowing him the way I do, I seriously doubt that he remembers
this pact at all.
You think he won't?
Not even a little.
Trust me, there's no reason for us to sweat this thing.
Well, okay, that's good news.
There's no reason for us to sweat it.
Although, that does kind of make me sad.
Huh?
I didn't say anything.
Besides, it doesn't really matter if we're engaged.
I don't need you.
I can make Kobito my sister all by myself.
I don't suppose I can convince you to give up on that, can I?
Whatever.
Let's go back to the club room.
Look, we may be fine, but I'm a little worried that Slozaro will get all pissy when she finds
out about it.
Well, we don't have to tell her about it, do we?
I mean, it doesn't matter anyway.
Yeah, I guess not.
Cool.
Let's go.
You're late!
What took so damn long?
Oh, nothing too important.
So are we gonna go film now or what?
Yes, we are.
Okay, let's roll.
We can start with the baseball field scene.
It's movie making time!
Maria?
What?
I'm just excited.
I like making movies with my big brother.
Movies, movies, movies are not made of...
I have this weird feeling like I'm forgetting something really important.
But you do have Senna, so, well, that's out.
Hold on.
If Kate thought Senna and I were together, I wonder if...
Right.
Are you and Senna really gonna get married?
The stupid hag told me yesterday that you guys were fiancés.
The word is fiancés, right?
I can't believe how grown up you must be.
If you get to have your very own fiancés, you're gonna get married!
Married people are grown-up fiancés!
Um, what is she talking about?
Huh?
They're betrothed.
And they met when they were, like, super little kids.
But it's no biggie.
What happened between our dads back then has nothing to do with us today.
Isn't that right?
That's right.
Yep, that's totally right!
Rika, I have a question.
Yes, Yozara?
How can Rika help you?
Do you think people who are childhood friends or engaged since before they can remember are closer?
Rika believes most people probably believe being betrothed is indeed closer.
That's what I thought.
Although I guess when you think about how long they've known each other,
one could consider them childhood friends as well.
That's what I thought.
Oh, come on! Will you get over it yourself?
We're saying it doesn't matter, so why are you being so dramatic?
If you can't step out of it on your own, let's see how...
Meat, you're going to regret that.
Great, just wonderful.
Can we go film something already?
Rika believes that Senna has a good point, Yozara.
There's no point in worrying about the promises our parents might have made.
What's more important is focusing on the here and now.
So where are we supposed to film today?
I don't know, but let's go make a movie!
Oh, whatever.
I don't even care anymore.
Wait! Big brother!
Hey, Kotaro. What is it?
It's Hirani. He's in trouble, and you've got to help him.
Oh, no!
Fine. Cut.
How do you think it went?
Well...
She's not with us, is she?
We might as well move on to the next scene for now.
Man, I'm so tired.
Huh?
What's up, big bro?
Like you even care.
Huh?
Today was a complete disaster, and it was all thanks to you.
I'm sorry?
I'm sorry.
I can see why you're so upset, and I do apologize.
But you should know we're not the only ones who've heard you and Senna are engaged.
I mean, it's pretty much accepted as a fact at this point.
Who?
Pegasus.
The guy talks about it every chance he gets.
I'd say it's safe to assume that all the faculty and sisters here know about it.
I'd bet some students think it's true, too.
Man, how can just one guy have such a big mouth?
I'm sure he was just excited, Kodaka.
How funny.
So Pegasus was jumping to conclusions.
Huh?
What did you say?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Okay, let's move on to something else.
I heard you guys are making a movie, huh?
Uh-huh.
What kind of movie is it, anyway?
I couldn't make heads or tails out of what Maria was trying to explain to me.
Yeah.
Yeah, I can believe that.
Oh, I see.
So it's a coming-of-age story based on a transfer student.
The more you tell me about it, the more it reminds me of that film Boys Over the Slope.
Really?
I've never even heard of that before.
Yep. It's another coming-of-age movie that most people consider a cult classic.
It's good. I'm surprised you don't know it.
You should watch it for research, at least.
Cool. That sounds like good reference material.
Great idea, Kate.
Wait, Big Brother!
Hey, Godaron, what is it?
It's tyranny. He-he's in trouble, and you've got to help him.
No way.
Yozara, how could she?
Why would she do something like this?
She plagiarized the entire script!
Okay, listen up.
I'll explain exactly what happened.
I thought Senna and Kodaka were dating,
but that apparently was not the case at all.
It may be hard to accept his truth.
I know I can barely believe it myself.
No need to get upset. Let's stay calm.
You seem almost happy about it, Kate.
No, no. I'm not happy in the least.
Next time...
The Sad Case King and the Stone Cold Story.
That Kodaka's got it rough, huh?
Maybe I have a chance with him now.
The Sad Case King's